[SPEAKER_01]: okay it's sunday morning now april 20th 1975 quarter after seven in the morning we're driving west on route 84 interstate 84 having left our motel room in new haven we have the joe wood interview on another tape that she had last night this side of this chalky tape is blank
[SPEAKER_01]: So I thought I'd put down some high points of our evening with Larry Ritter, which was on Thursday night, April 18, at the Nash OAH convention in Boston.
[SPEAKER_01]: OK, now we met Ritter at the panel in the morning.
[SPEAKER_01]: and didn't have much chance to talk to him about his book and his method of interviewing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I suggested maybe we could meet for dinner if he was going to be around.
[SPEAKER_01]: He didn't think he was going to be around.
[SPEAKER_01]: He thought he'd be leaving, but he wanted to see some people and he'd let me know later.
[SPEAKER_01]: It turned out he was going to be able to stay over, so we met for dinner.
[SPEAKER_01]: I must have spent a couple of hours there.
[SPEAKER_01]: We met about a quarter after seven, down in the dining room of the Statler Hilton.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'd probably break up to around nine o'clock.
[SPEAKER_01]: He paid the bill, by the way, which was, as things turned out, very helpful.
[SPEAKER_01]: I out-fumbled him.
[SPEAKER_01]: The way his idea originated for interviewing was that he was recently separated and then divorced.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure if he was already divorced when it began.
[SPEAKER_01]: He only had his son, who was then 13 years old.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was in 1961.
[SPEAKER_01]: He only had his son certain times of the year, like in summer vacations.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he'd always been a baseball fan, and this was something to do, going around interviewing people.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he brought his son along with him.
[SPEAKER_01]: He insists he traveled 75,000 miles, although he only interviewed 35 people, which averages out about two
[SPEAKER_01]: over 2,000 miles a person.
[SPEAKER_01]: He made a number of trips to the West Coast, but he apparently did not get all of his West Coast interviews in one trip.
[SPEAKER_01]: He took them more leisurely when he apparently had funds enough to go back and forth.
[SPEAKER_01]: He used an old, big wall and sack type tape recorder, which weighed a great deal and had to be carried around.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he, in one of his interviews,
[SPEAKER_01]: He had a hernia developed from the weight carrying that thing around.
[SPEAKER_01]: His son carried it some of the time later on.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was a little bigger, but he wasn't big enough to carry it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: He wasn't with him, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it may have been the Paul Wainer interview.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or maybe Cravath.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know who it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess he didn't see Cravath, but it was one of his
[SPEAKER_01]: one of his interviews where he misread the number on the house where he was going it's 32 and he was going to 42 or something and he so he got off at the other number here's a car he got off at the other number and had to walk back there was about 10 houses or was it 10 blocks 10 houses
[SPEAKER_01]: and he felt this something give his groin.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess he went ahead with the interview, but he was complaining about the weight of these recorders for carrying them around, which I well appreciate having done it myself, how much better it is with these small cassette recorders.
[SPEAKER_01]: He planned his interviews by getting a map of the United States, getting a copy of Smalling's directory to all living baseball players, and then mapping out his route.
[SPEAKER_01]: He would usually stay near national parks,
[SPEAKER_01]: so that they could visit the park.
[SPEAKER_01]: He didn't care much about the park himself, but his son did.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they mixed in a lot of tourism with their interviewing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't camp.
[SPEAKER_01]: As I can see, they stayed in motels.
They're in formation here.
[SPEAKER_01]: The guy wouldn't pick up or fall back.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they planned his trip that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: That made me wonder why he didn't get all of his West Coast people on one trip if he planned it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I didn't ask about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't want to.
[SPEAKER_01]: indicate that he didn't plan it very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: He would send letters in advance describing what he was doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure what he would give as a return address because he must have been on the road when he wrote some of these letters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he'd write them all before he left and set up, see if they'd see him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't hear him say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he never set a definite date for when he'd be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's never tied down.
[SPEAKER_01]: When he would get in the area.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to miss a turn.
[SPEAKER_01]: When he would then get to that area, he would either call or write again.
[SPEAKER_01]: probably call and set up a definite time and then go on out to the interview.
[SPEAKER_01]: He would spend the day before he should going over the record of the player and record books and so on until he knew the man's record better than he did when he went into the interview.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sounds like he went over it much more carefully than I do when I go to mine.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least I don't know if he takes an actual copy of the record with him or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: He knows it very well before he goes in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of the interviews lasted, well they averaged from one to three hours it sounded like.
[SPEAKER_01]: There were a few occasions where he had time and they were interested and it might begin in the evening and they'd resume the next day.
[SPEAKER_01]: But some of them were, I got the idea, most of them didn't run more than two and a half to three hours, probably a lot like my interviews.
[SPEAKER_01]: His longest one at one stretch was Paul Wainer, where he arrived there about eight o'clock and kept going on and on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Larry Ritter was ready to quit any time knowing it might be tiring his subject, but Paul Weiner said no, he's a night person.
[SPEAKER_01]: He went out until two o'clock at that time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's Paul Weiner.
[SPEAKER_01]: So the interview was varying like some an hour, some an hour and a half, two hours, a few, three hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: Occasionally, I think Sam Crawford is the one that went on the next day, and he began again in the morning.
[SPEAKER_01]: And since he was on no very tight time schedule, he couldn't stay over, he couldn't plan for those three days.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as subjects go, he was turned down by, he interviewed all, look at it, 35 people.
[SPEAKER_01]: 22 people were in the book, Glory of Their Times.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other 13 either said what was already said by somebody else better, so he picked one of the two, or wouldn't,
[SPEAKER_01]: would let their interview be printed.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only one he spoke of in this connection was Billy Werber.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had a good interview with him, and then he sent the manuscript of the Werber material, which would be in the book to him for confirmation.
[SPEAKER_01]: that if that was printed you would deny it all.
[SPEAKER_01]: In other words, he didn't want any of it printed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why this change about he doesn't know unless maybe Werber is bringing out a book of his own?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we heard that later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, did we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we heard that from Art Gray.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, is that what we heard then?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he might want to keep this, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: Supposed to have one coming out shortly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to blow the lid off, all kinds of people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then this interview is over ten years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why would they be holding things up then?
[SPEAKER_01]: He had a few turndowns.
[SPEAKER_01]: And one of his biggest turndowns is Joe McCarthy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another turned down was Duffy Lewis, who I got turned down on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another is Joe Dugan.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he had a few more.
[SPEAKER_01]: They would give various excuses, but he concluded that no matter what the excuse was, it was just they didn't want to be interviewed.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were trying to let you down because they knew you wouldn't be in the area again.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if they could put you off a little bit, they were safe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any other turndowns you can remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I can never remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just forgot about them.
[SPEAKER_02]: He doesn't even...
[SPEAKER_02]: When we first asked him, he said he hardly had any.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the more names I mentioned, the more people, it seemed like everybody I named had been turned down.
[SPEAKER_01]: He thought Joe McCarthy, the fact that we interviewed Joe McCarthy was a minor miracle almost.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get that impression?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because he had turned down that other guy who has that book coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Setting up the interview, he would just chat amiably with the subject while his son was setting up the tape recorder, looking around for bass plugs, putting the recorder out of sight behind the chair.
[SPEAKER_01]: They developed a pattern or a system there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that they would have the whole thing set up very...
[SPEAKER_02]: Pardon me, you just took Exit 20.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, for the record.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure I saw 84 there.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Make sure we're on the right road here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exit 20 and off here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or was I?
[SPEAKER_01]: Shutting up the interview.
[SPEAKER_01]: Newberg.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they would proceed with the interview and very soon they would forget all about the tape recorder.
Because they always had it hidden.
Yeah, because it's hidden.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, I don't hide them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I stick them right between myself and the interviewee because I have the built-in microphone like this one.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's just more convenient.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to do it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: You pick up the voices.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the thing itself is not very conspicuous.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joe Wood kept pointing to it when he didn't want to be recorded.
[SPEAKER_01]: We shut it off, but I don't think it's that important.
[SPEAKER_01]: They occasionally look at it, but they kind of forget it too.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is not as big as the other.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't see the tape turning like you do in that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't see volume, flashes, flashing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think maybe the improved technology has reduced that problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: They always had the big recorder.
[SPEAKER_01]: He would begin his questioning with some hot questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: This may be a good way to do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And his big questions, key questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: He wanted to make sure that he got the most important questions asked unless something happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then he would fill in and work back or forward.
[SPEAKER_01]: as opposed to my chronological approach.
[SPEAKER_01]: My chronological approach blew a fuse with McCarthy because I was just getting up to some good things when he ran out of steam.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it was shocking last night I was more topical than chronological, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Wood last night.
[SPEAKER_01]: What'd I say?
[SPEAKER_01]: Shocking?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: With Joe Wood last night, I approached him more topically than chronologically.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I may have to keep this in mind in the future.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was always running out of tape.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got Paul Wader in our view.
[SPEAKER_01]: He went at 2 o'clock and he ran out of tape about 11 o'clock at night.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't imagine running out of tape.
[SPEAKER_01]: Planning everything so carefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not having enough tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it probably took two hours or three hours worth of tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if it went on, because those were bulky to carry, and he probably didn't go in with.
[SPEAKER_01]: He only did two hours in one row on those things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he probably didn't carry anything else in with the tape recorder.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's what I say.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's got his kid carrying and helping him out.
[SPEAKER_01]: He probably didn't want to walk in with all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: His first and only time, maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't have enough tape.
I can't see that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because probably when you interview, instead of having to take the time out to plug everything in, take the cellophane off the tape, tape the tape, you should probably have the tape and the tape recorder and everything plugged in so that it's done in a minute without that time in there that, while you're getting set up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You think that would help?
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably would.
[SPEAKER_01]: My biggest problem is getting that cellophane off the paper carton.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, just last night I noticed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never noticed it before.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's got to be a shot if you've got to put that stuff on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no release on the cellophane.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got to fight your way into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gouges your thumbnail.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have I left some things out now?
[SPEAKER_01]: What was our general conversation about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you've covered it very well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll shut it off to think of something then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_01]: We asked him about how many copies of the book sold.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said 150,000 copies sold.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hardback.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hardback.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's out of print now.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't print anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: He can't understand why.
[SPEAKER_01]: We figured out at $10 a book or so.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did you have?
[SPEAKER_02]: You came up with some big figure that he might have made, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said he probably made well over $100,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: The paperback is still available.
[SPEAKER_01]: He doesn't know how many copies it sold.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he does get a commitment of royalty on that, too?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joe Wood last night brought in the glory of their times with Ritter's having written a little personal note in the front of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He probably gave those to all the ones he used to interview.
[SPEAKER_01]: He gave all of his tapes to the Hall of Fame and was asked only in return, this is what he told me, he crossed for the tape
[SPEAKER_01]: Then he said he got $5,000, that's all he got from it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we don't know how he could have paid $5,000 worth of tapes for just 35 tapes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it must have been something more to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But he said all of his materials
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like he gave them grant.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's when you hear him talk about it at first.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he'd get $5,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's expenses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that'd help cover his vacations to the west.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I don't think it was subsidized.
[SPEAKER_01]: It could have been subsidized by the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
I wonder about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: because I mentioned to him about Ken Smith.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were up there in 64 and how Ken Smith said was just interviewing Warrens or had a tape of Warren Spahn he was playing and I talked to him about taped interviews of old ball players and he said he wasn't interested in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ritter said that those interviews Ken Smith got were instructional types, how to pitch, how to bat, that kind of thing, not historical types.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I don't, I forgot what he said now about Smith's attitude towards the...
[SPEAKER_02]: He said he was in favor of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who did he negotiate his thing with?
[SPEAKER_01]: Caracoin?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Paul Kerr.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jack Fine didn't know anything about this before he was there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lee Allen was the historian.
[SPEAKER_01]: He negotiated for the transfer of the tapes with Kerr, maybe with Ken Smith and Lee Allen.
[SPEAKER_01]: They got 5,000 bucks for them, and the stipulation was that they should be open and available for use to anybody who wanted to use them.
[SPEAKER_01]: He also set forth some suggestions as to how to store and house the tapes in rooms of certain temperatures and in atmospheric conditions where the tapes would not deteriorate.
[SPEAKER_01]: He also talked a little bit about the use of tapes which are stored.
[SPEAKER_01]: They should be played every year.
[SPEAKER_01]: They should be run through at least one site every year and then repackaged because they tend to deteriorate when they're never played at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: He would do it that frequently, but he would say at least every five years, each tape should be run through.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not run through, but played through.
[SPEAKER_01]: not fast forward, but actually played at a slow pace, giving the tape a chance to get exposed to the air.
[SPEAKER_01]: He made all these recommendations to Paul when he gave him his tapes, but he doesn't know if they paid any attention to him or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: When he sold them his tapes, I think is a better word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: He sold them his tapes about a year after the book came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: He got rid of them right away in 1967.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's perfectly willing that I could make copies if I wanted to, if they would permit it.
[SPEAKER_01]: He did make a stipulation that they must let anybody listen to the tapes, but he doesn't know if copying them would be included in that stipulation.
[SPEAKER_01]: I could tell him if I go up there that he
[SPEAKER_01]: He said it's perfectly all right and he would like to have them make copies for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me copy them if I want to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure they won't if they pay $5,000 for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're probably right on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's now about seven minutes before eight.
We're crossing over the Hudson River at Newburgh.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought you might want to know about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was talking about other matters that came up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I asked Ritter what he had been doing after the book was out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't this leave a void in his life?
[SPEAKER_01]: He was editor of the Journal of Finance in 1964 to 1966, just as he was wrapping the book up, so he had a lot of... all of these things were going on full speed at the same time.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said no, he needed the time to get his own professional work sorted out.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was so far back in everything that
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the glory of their times came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: He then had a little bit of free time to get other things done, get caught up in his reading and his own work.
[SPEAKER_01]: But since that time, he's done nothing in baseball.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's kept up his interest greatly and knows a lot and has a library, but he hasn't
[SPEAKER_01]: done anymore with any baseball projects.
[SPEAKER_01]: He lives in an apartment, I think he's had a two-bedroom apartment there on 73rd Street and some intersection in New York City.
[SPEAKER_01]: He teaches at the downtown
[SPEAKER_01]: New York University campus, Washington Square campus.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do I do here now?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we wouldn't get off, but we would stay in.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're now in great old Newburgh.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had four rejections.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's one point.
[SPEAKER_01]: I asked him about how he peddled this, and he said,
[SPEAKER_01]: before he finally found a publisher.
[SPEAKER_01]: I asked him how the idea of the book actually developed, and he said he didn't have an idea of a book, he was just doing it for pleasure, the interviews, to get his mind diverted from his domestic difficulties.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the players he interviewed kept asking him what he was going to do with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he said, well, I'm going to write a book.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least it's something to say.
[SPEAKER_01]: And after he would leave them, Christmas would come around.
[SPEAKER_01]: He'd get Christmas cards from all these people saying, where's the book?
[SPEAKER_01]: Want to read about it in the book?
[SPEAKER_01]: So he decided to put out a book.
[SPEAKER_01]: He kind of chuckled.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, it was a little more complex than that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the way he put it was rather amusing.
[SPEAKER_01]: He has had quite a library of baseball materials, but he's had to dispose of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I just don't remember now what he said he did have, but it wasn't very expensive after he had to get rid of some of it because of the storage problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: He just didn't have enough space.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yes, one other thing about the selling of the tapes to Cooperstown.
[SPEAKER_01]: This might be part of the price involved.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's got a complete transcript of every interview.
[SPEAKER_01]: For an hour of interview, you have maybe like 30 typed pages.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe that's high, but I think that's what he said.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he's got more than just the tapes.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have the typed transcript for all those interviews.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he said...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's starting to rain a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had his girlfriend do most of the typing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they broke up as soon as she was through.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, well, I don't know that she was through.
[SPEAKER_01]: He got some people at the college, at the university, in his office to do some of the typing, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did he say about using the Xerox machine at the college and charging it to his department?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said he could do as much as he wanted, so he didn't have her do carbons.
[SPEAKER_01]: He just Xeroxed them.
[SPEAKER_01]: He didn't have her type the sub-machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but there'd been some healthy Xerox bill.
[SPEAKER_01]: Those are back in the days of affluence.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he has those type transcripts.
[SPEAKER_01]: And when he put the book together, he worked from the transcripts rather than tapes.
[SPEAKER_01]: He used the tapes.
[SPEAKER_01]: He listened to them to get in the mood, to get the tone of voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do I do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Go straight ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he would listen to the tape to get the feel of the voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did he put it?
[SPEAKER_01]: He had a phrase he used there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then after that, he would go to the type strip because he couldn't keep playing the tape over and over again, running back to find those points he wanted.
[SPEAKER_01]: He had the type copy there and words from that to select those portions which he would include in the book.
[SPEAKER_00]: He was hit by a pitched ball, not once, but twice.
[SPEAKER_00]: At the close of that baseball game, the figures in the daily box score beside Ray Chaplin's name read like this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Times a bat, twice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hits, two.
[SPEAKER_00]: Run scored, two.
[SPEAKER_00]: stolen bases, two.
[SPEAKER_00]: In the field, it was put outs, two.
[SPEAKER_00]: Assists, two.
[SPEAKER_00]: Inners, two.
[SPEAKER_00]: A month ago, I told you that he wasn't hit once, but twice.
[SPEAKER_00]: On his last time at bat, the seventh inning, Ray Chapman was struck by a pitch ball for the second time that afternoon.
[SPEAKER_00]: He completed the cycle of two four hits.
[SPEAKER_00]: and soon after, the Great Shore stop was there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ironically, it was two o'clock the next morning when Ray Chapman closed his eyes forever.
[SPEAKER_00]: And had not Bob Prince thought about yesterday, or last night, I should say, in the game of the St. Louis Cardinals, I might have perhaps forgotten a story that I wanted to tell you this afternoon.
[SPEAKER_00]: And on the day for the Bush Stadium, or the Cardinal game, with Bill Buckle.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye!